hackerthemes.com 2019-06-04

# HackerThemes

Your privacy is important to us.

It is HackerThemes’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * We will not sell or rent your personal information to any third party.
  * We do not store credit card information. Credit card payments are handled via [Paddle](https://paddle.com/). 
  * We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We use cookies to improve your user experience on our site.
  * We use Google Analytics to collect usage statistics about our visitors.
  * We may use your email address to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 
  * We may release personal information if we are required to by law, search warrant, subpoena, court order or fraud investigation. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. HackerThemes may change this privacy policy from time to time at HackerThemes’s sole discretion.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
